outlettable.com 2016-03-23

# Privacy Policy - Outlet Sheet

Updated Date: November 6, 2012

We attach great importance to your privacy. Our website (OutletSheet.com) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and providing a safe online environment for all our users. This Privacy Policy mainly describes your privacy rights in relation to our collection, use, storage, sharing, and protection of your personal information collected through your website use. Please read the policy carefully and contact us if you have any questions. This Privacy Policy is updated from time to time, therefore it should be reviewed frequently.

 **1\. Information Collection**

You can browse our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. When you visit our website or use our application or our services, data can be collected and processed through your operations. The types of personal information we collect through different ways are as follows.  
1.1 Personal information collected during your communication with our personnel or website. If you have any questions and suggestions and communicate with us by emails or other manners, we may collect your information.  
1.2 Device Information. We may collect information about the computer, mobile phone, or other device you use to access the Services to measure the effectiveness of those Services.  
1.3 Cookies. We may use cookies to gather information regarding our services in a mathematical collection for our website and our advertisers. Any information collected will not have any identifying data. It is statistical data about our visitors and how they have used our website. We may assemble information about your common Internet use with a cookie file. The information sought by the cookie helps us improve our website and any service offered to you.  
1.4 Analytics. We may use third parties to provide us information, reports and analysis about the usage and browsing patterns of users of the Services. These reports contain aggregated data only, and do not identify individual users.  
1.5 IP Addresses. We log Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We use this information to track access to our website and mobile applications.  
1.6 Log Files. We may also automatically log certain usage information about your use of the Services. This information includes a reading history of the pages you view. Through this we can learn more about your use of our website and improve our service on the website.

 **2\. Our Use of Your Information**

The information we collect regarding your use of our website is applied to help us improve our services and provide better online experience for our users. We may use the information from the several ways below.  
2.1 We may use your information for statistical analysis. Your information which can reflect your browsing of our website is used to analyze the use of different services provided on the website so that we can make targeted improvement and enhancement according to the service condition. We can also make full use of this information to let advertisers be well-informed of the nature of our user base.  
2.2 We may use the information to customize your experience. We use the information to let advertising be targeted to the users for whom such advertising is most pertinent. We may also use this information to customize certain features of the Services to provide you with an enhanced experience based on the type of device you are using to access the Services, and to provide you with requested services.  
2.3 We may use the information to help our company better understand our users (what they do on our websites, what website features they like, how they use them, etc.) and to improve the content and answers delivered on the Services.

 **3\. Information Storage**

We store and process your personal information on our computers in Houston, Texas, United States, where our facilities are located. We protect your information using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls.

 **4\. Information Disclosure**

We disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.  
We may also disclose the information to staff members in our company to provide joint content and services, to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, websites, applications, tools, services and communications.  
Third Party disclosure may occur for the following reasons: Selling any or all of our business to a third party may result in sharing your information; at any time when we are legally required to we may disclose information about you and your visits to our websites.  
Without the above conditions and special legal requirements, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information.

 **5\. Disclaimer**

We believe that maintaining and preserving the privacy of user data is an important value. This Privacy Policy, together with other policies, resolutions, and actions by our company, represents a committed effort to safeguard the security of the limited user information that is collected and retained on our servers. Nevertheless, we cannot guarantee that user information will remain private. We acknowledge that, in spite of our committed effort to protect private user information, determined individuals may still develop data-mining and other methods to uncover such information and disclose it.

 **6\. Third Party Links**

Third party links may be discovered on our website. These third party links have their own privacy policy, which you agree to when you click on the link. We are not responsible nor do we accept responsibility for third party links. Our liability covers us only on our website, and thus we do not accept liability for third party links as we have no control over them.

 **7\. Contact Information**

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions, requests or comments about our Privacy Policy. We appreciate your communication with us by emails via the email address supplied here: support(AT)outletlocation(DOT)com.

Please Note: The trademarks of all the merchants listed on the website are the sole property of their respective owners. The website is not affiliated with any of them. For any inquiry relating to a specific brand or mall, please contact the merchant directly.
